Just hit me.
That's why you followed me.
What a bad luck to came across you.
Will San come back to me if I hit you?
Okay, I'll hit you.
I'll hit you a hundred of times.
I'm sorry.
I hate you.
Why?
What is it?
You bitch!
What happened to San?
What do you mean?
San is dead.
Parole?
My friend betrayed me.
I would've gotten 3 more years for another crime.
They asked me to prevent you from getting parole.
If I made you cause some small trouble,
they'd let me go.
I did what they asked me to do.
Yujeong, have you offended anyone?
You're not a person who'd do anything wrong,
so I thought I could do something do the child.
He asked me to do that.
He said he would take care of San. I swear.
Stay in jail.
When you get out, I'll make your life miserable.
You should suffer as much as I did.
You should know how it feels when you lose your loved ones.
You have to realise how painful it is.
Hey! Designated driver!
What are you doing so late at night?
Who were you meeting?
Do I have to answer this question?
What?
Though I owe you money,
I don't have the obligation to report my every move to you.
Well...
Are you running away?
You don't like drinking?
You can't run away like this.
As a man.
I don't just let people die like some people I know.
Prosecutor An, don't you think you are shameless?
You put her in jail yet you didn't flinch.
Were there any other witnesses?
I'm not sure.
I transferred all the files to the procuratorial organ.
It's been 4 years, so why?
Did she say something the other day?
Did she claim herself to be innocent?
Call me if you remember something.
K Corporation Legal Team...
Wait! It reminds me of something.
A witness came to me,
gave me a K Corporation business card,
and asked me to contact him if I found anything.
Who is he?
Wait a minute, I might have his business card here.
Sorry.
Prosecutor. No, lawyer. You can't do this.
You should apply to the court to see the files.
Prosecutor An.
Mr. Kim. I heard that your son got a job at K Construction.
But he originally applied for the K Hotel, right?
Take your time.
The camera is too old, and the image isn't clear.
It's impossible to identify the driver.
It took me a long time to find the license plate number.
If we find the black box from this car,
we might be able to find the drum that the defendant saw.
If we have the driver's face on the black box,
she won't be able to deny it any longer.
This car is very common to see, so it's hard to find.
Sir, you're staying up so late.
What are you doing in my office?
I came here to see you.
When will you announce to investigate K Corporation?
I know people can change,
but I was surprised to see you change so fast.
When did you become a spokesman of K Corporation?
I have some information related to Jaegyeong Corporation,
if you stop this investigation...
Now you're making deals.
You were good at first.
Money talks.
Be careful. There's no free lunch.
Minhyeok looks like a spoiled rich kid,
but he's like his father.
Thank you for your advice.
You haven't slept all night,
and you got up so early.
What happened?
Drink it. You didn't even have dinner.
My son, San.
If he were born in another family,
he would be happy.
That's nonsense.
It's San because you gave birth to him.
If not, he'd be a stranger.
What's wrong with you?
I miss San so much.
Sister.
Sir.
What?
Can I ask you something?
Do you keep black box recordings of executives' cars?
Why do you ask?
I want to use them as evidence to prove that Congressman Shin and President Jo are innocent.
The security team has them.
Call me if necessary.
Thank you.
What a beautiful view.
What are you doing here?
You seem angry.
Why do you think I'm here?
I have no time to chat with you.
Do you like my present?
You used to tell me
that we were different and we wouldn't be friends.
I guess you were right.
Don't overestimate yourself just because you can get access to my home.
The K Corporation is mine.
And stay away from Seyeon.
You can't even protect your own woman,
how dare you flirt with other guy's woman?
Keep up the good work. For my company.
Hello.
Sorry. I've busy preparing this event.
Let's continue.
Yes.
Why didn't you contact me after you left that day?
Why didn't you contact me first?
Could you please give this to Mr. Jo?
Sir. A woman left it here.
This is what I saved up in jail, and the money my father left.
I'll work harder to save up more,
Where did she go?
She went out that way.
Driver!
Hello.
How dare you!
How dare you not answering my call.
I'm answering you now.
All right.
Why did you give me those money?
I'll send it to you once a month.
No.
I'll decide how you pay me back.
I didn't say I would accept your plan.
Come to the hotel tomorrow.
Are you there?
I have something very important to do tomorrow.
How dare you disobey me?
Sorry, I can't cancel tomorrow's schedule.
Bye.
Tomorrow...
How dare she!
Gwangsu!
Yes, sir!
What's Kang Yujeong's schedule tomorrow?
Did she find a new part time job?
Caught just off the coast.
They're very fresh.
Sir! Madam! Come and take a look.
Mackerels and herrings, they're very fresh.
Take a look.
- Come again. - What?
When did she start coming here?
- The mackerel is fresh. - She started coming here after she got out of jail.
They're not that good.
They're very fresh.
Why didn't you tell me earlier?
You told me to stop following her around.
Since when did you become so obedient?
Look, these are very fresh.
Beautiful lady, come and have a look.
No? Come again.
Take care.
Sir! Don't you like mackerel?
No.
It's delicious to stew them.
I told you not to come again, why are you still here?
Madam, I'll do it.
Go away.
Let me...
Take them with you.
I'll enjoy it, thank you.
I'll come back again.
Why are you hiding?
What are you doing here? This isn't your place.
I spend half of my salary on rent, I have nothing to eat.
Right?
I'm older than you, show your respect to me.
He's my boss. He's my boss.
So what? Let me go!
He's your boss, not my boss.
What's this?
How can you say that?
Excuse her, she used to be a polite girl.
How do you do? I'm Sandra Hwang.
You have beautiful eyes. Are you married?
You might get hurt.
Do you know him?
We're having dinner. Would you like to join us?
Sandra, he's my boss.
He won't eat something like this.
How picky he is.
How come he can't eat such delicious food?
Watch your mouth!
I'm so sorry.
Let's eat together.
Have a seat.
She is actually kind,
but she's got a foul mouth.
Aren't you hungry?
The fish looks good.
With some soup.
Take this as my apology. Come on.
Ah!
That's right.
Eating comes first anyway.
Don't you know she can't stand fishy smell?
She only likes sweet stuff.
Would you like a drink?
I'll have one.
Me, too.
Let's make a toast.
If you want to talk to me, come in.
What is it now?
If you can't stand fishy smells, why do you sell seafood?
How shameless you are.
How dare you go to see her?
You know I had a son.
He was taken away from me in jail.
I couldn't be there when he died.
He was really sick,
but I couldn't hold him in my arms.
I only had him for a year, and it hurts so much.
Seo Jihui's mother must be desperate when her daughter passed away since she raised her for so many years.
I'll atone for my sin against her for the rest of my life.
I know I can't undo what I did.
But...
I can't run away though it hurts so much.
Sir!
I can't make it.
You shouldn't have gotten into debt.
You said you wouldn't run away.
Don't pretend to be nice.
Are you going to cry again?
Don't cry.
I don't want to see your cheap tears.
Hey.
Gwangsu. The worse I treat her, the more it hurts me.
I'm An Dohun.
Okay.
Why isn't it working?
It's not?
That's strange.
Stay inside, okay?
Okay.
Sir?
Yes.
Would you like some coffee?
Yes. Thank you
You're welcome.
What are you doing here so late?
I have no obligation to tell you what I do after my working time.
I'm familiar with such expression.
Someone who were caught doing something other than work at the company would have such an expression.
Right?
We've known each other for over 4 years.
I feel like I know a lot of things about you.
If you knew how much I know about you,
you might be scared.
That's too bad.
I don't know much about you.
Ah! Except one thing.
You're nothing without your father.
This is the only thing I know.
I've walked on a thin sheet of ice.
I am worried that the ice would break and I would fell into water.
I'm worried that I would disappoint my parents.
I'm worried that I would crawl back to where I started.
I've made it this far by trying so hard.
What about you?
How do you make this far?
Marriage?
Is that why you're using Seyeon like this?
You said you are her friend.
Don't do that to her.
Don't do that to your friend.
Okay. I'll check it right away.
Your line's been busy, so...
I'll call you later.
Okay.
What are you doing here?
I need to check some artwork transactions between the Shina Gallery and the K Corporation.
Really?
Does this painting have that much value?
The value of a work of art is a relative concept.
When President Jo decides to buy it,
the value of the paining goes up.
I guess it goes the same with people.
Depending on who sees that person,
he can be valuable or worthless.
I know this isn't what you want.
Your father and President Jo did it.
But I was the one who closed those deals.
It doesn't matter.
No matter what happens, I won't let you get hurt.
Read it.
You can find out how revenge, which started because of love, ended.
Gwangsu, do you still believe in love?
Yes.
Why?
The world is better with love than without it.
Thank you for your cooperation.
I need to be at the prosecutor's office tomorrow morning. I have to go.
I don't know much about you.
Except one thing.
You're nothing without your father.
Is that why you're using Seyeon like this?
You said you were her friend.
It sucks.
The Hotel Rating Inspection starts today.
Before the judges arrive...
Why are you looking at me like that?
You said our marriage
is a deal.
Do you really think so?
Yes.
We both signed the contract.
You look good.
It's good to see you working so hard for my company so early in the morning.
Where are you going in such a hurry?
Since it's working hours, I guess you should tell me now.
I'm working hard so that your father won't have to sit in a wheelchair to work again.
I'm busy.
Since when did you worry about my father's health?
You'll fell relieved if your father is healthy.
Enough!
Minhyeok! What's the matter with you?
Don't side with him in front of me.
Excuse me.
You claimed him to be your friend.
He's also my friend.
You'll find out soon,
if he is a good friend or a bad friend.
Seyeon, look at this.
I didn't notice it this morning. I thought the fragrance came from elsewhere.
Then I found it blossom.
Isn't it pretty?
It's parasitic orchid.
Don't you think it's like a beautiful lady?
Look at it. It has no leaves.
This can only live off another plant.
Thus its name.
Isn't it just like me?
Seyeon.
Don't be too perfect in front of Minhyeok.
You're too smart and beautiful.
Men instinctively don't like girls who are more excellent.
I don't care.
Whether he likes or not,
he has to marry me.
Okay.
Enjoy your meal.
Thank you.
Be careful.
OK. Thank you.
Okay.
Honey! Honey!
Isn't that Dohun? Oh my god.
Our son is so handsome.
Welcome.
Welcome, take a seat there please.
Rich people always get away with what they did.
Educated ones always get along with rich guys.
They learn how to lie with their good brains.
There's no use to learn so many things.
Let's drink.
Excuse me!
Bring us some noodles.
Okay.
There's an accusation that the K Corporation transferred money to politicians through the Shina Gallery. Is that true?
It's not true.
The Shina Gallery
is a nonprofit organization which cultivates talented young artists.
It has nothing to do with political fund.
To clear our name, the K Corporation will cooperate with the investigation.
If we've done anything illegal, I'll escort President Jo to the press conference.
Thank you.
Hello.
It's unbelievable that Haeri treat us to such a good dinner.
I might move to your place.
Of course I need to treat you.
Thank you, Haeri.
It's so dry. I want something with soup.
Eat this, I'll get you more, madam.
Okay. Bring us some soup, okay?
We'd like to have seafood soup.
Haeri.
I saw a notice looking for a waitress at the front door.
We have one position left to fill.
This is great. Come with me.
Sir! Have you found a new waitress?
Why do you ask that?
I want you to consider her, she has a lot of experience doing part-time jobs.
She is experienced in different fields.
I can assure you that she is the best.
Is that so? What's your name?
Kang Yujeong.
Have you ever worked in restaurants?
Yes. I've worked at fast food restaurants since high school,
I also worked at hotel buffet restaurants, coffee shops, fancy restaurants...
OK. Since Haeri vouched for you, you can have a one week probation.
Thank you so much. You won't regret it.
Take this home. Your parents will like it.
They're fresh.
Come back again.
Ma'am. Fresh mackerel. They're fresh and fleshy.
Do you think I'll forgive you as long as you do something like this?
What's this for?
You said the culprit saw Jihui,
but walked away, right?
That's what the evidence says.
We found the footprints going near her and then lead away from her.
Are you sure they were female footprints?
Because of the rain, it was hard to determine shape or size.
but we used them as evidence that the culprit knew the situation.
It's possible they weren't Kang's footprints.
Why do you keep digging into a closed case?
Dohun checked the same file the other day as well.
Who?
An Dohun.
An Dohun?
What? What's wrong?
They'll start an investigation,
They won't take any action now.
But you'd better not do anything that'll draw attention.
Attention?
The biggest problem for the K Corporation
is not the prosecution, but Jo Minhyeok.
An Dohun!
Go ahead.
The board members aren't satisified with your son at the moment.
The K Hotel's having financial problems,
and there's only so much Seyeon can do.
They all know about your health problem as well.
What are you talking about?
How many times president Jo has been to Germany in the past 2 years
you are more aware of it than me.
I used to think it had something to do with overseas investment,
but I was wrong.
How bad is your health?
It will take Minhyeok a long time
to take over the K Corporation.
Is Minhyeok in his room?
He doesn't start until this afternoon.
Take Dohun to his room.
Persuade him.
Maybe he'll grow up when someone hurts his dignity.
He'll be here soon. Wait here.
Thank you.
Watch your mouth. Don't say too much.
We've known each other for over 4 years, I feel like I know a lot of things about you.
If you knew how much I know about you, you might be scared.
What are you doing in my room?
You inflated the price of the Incheon Hotel. Where's the rest of the money?
I heard that the K Hotel put pressure on the union
while ignoring the Labor Committee's advice.
They could impose a business suspension. Don't you know that?
That's why I hired you.
Thousands of people's jobs are on the line.
I hope you can be more serious.
How dare you?
You seem to forget the reality.
I'm the owner and I know that more than anyone.
You can just do what I tell you to do.
Okay.
About Kang Yujeong.
She was the woman I used to love.
Treat her with respect.
I don't know what you're trying to do to her.
But I won't be at the mercy of you anymore.
The hit-and-run occurred 4 years ago.
I wonder why
you had to look up the investigation report again.
We have to go. Your father is waiting for you.
Okay.
I should've poured that for you.
Thanks to you, we passed the rating inspection.
As long as you know.
You heard about the party next week, right? Are you coming?
Let me think about it.
Seyeon!
Suppose I killed someone.
And I had to go to jail. What would you do?
I'd hire the best lawyer,
I'd meet the prosecutor, the judge,
or even the chief justice, if I had to.
What if I still had to go to jail?
You wouldn't go to jail.
I wouldn't let you.
Shit.
Dohun.
What's going on?
We're friends, right?
Right.
Can I ask you a favor, as a friend?
Can you make some time next Wednesday?
Is this about the party that Minhyeok's hosting?
Yes.
Okay.
Can you tell me why?
Are you trying to draw attention from Minhyeok?
Or do you really want to go with me?
Well, Minhyeok is...
I'll go. I heard your answer.
Good work, prosecutor An.
You did a better job than I had expected.
Putting aside any personal feelings, you only follow the law.
Trust me. No one was there. I didn't see anybody.
A truck just jumped out in front of us,
and the car slipped, and we...
No! I... I hit the drum in the construction site nearby.
No, this can't be true. I don't know.
I didn't hit anyone.
Because of the rain, it was hard to tell the shape or size,
But we found footprints walking away from the victim.
It's possible they weren't Kang's footprints.
I don't think I paid for what I did.
I won't forget it as long as I live.
I'm ashamed of what I did to that woman.
Gwangsu.
Yes, sir.
Dig deeper.
How are you going pay me back working like this?
That's why I'm working hard.
Don't interrupt me if you want your money.
What are you doing?
On the night of the accident, you saw Jihui, and walked away. Right?
Did you really see her and walk away?
Yes! I did it. What more do you want from me?
Haven't you tortured me enough for all these years?
When can you pay me back by doing this?
You want to stop seeing me, right?
Go with me.
Put this on her.
Please come with me.
I...
If you do what I ask you to do today,
I'll deduct this month's debt.
Driver.
Sorry.
That's all right.
I don't like the design.
Try this one.
Good.
I remember. It was 4 years ago?
Can you give me more details?
Where is Minhyeok? Why are you here alone?
This is Attorney An Dohun
from the K Corporation Legal Team.
What? Are you exchanging partner with each other?
Who is that girl?
Don't mind her. She does everything Minhyeok asks her to do
to pay back the debt that she owes him.
Seyeon.
What is it? What do you want to do?
Sorry! I didn't know you'd come today.
Is that why you brought her here?
No...
I never said I wouldn't come.
When you asked me,
I said I'd think about it.
What's wrong with you?
I told you that I'd deal with him
by myself.
I didn't know you'd be here.
If I weren't here, you'd follow him anywhere?
What are you wearing?
I had no choice. He forced me to do it.
If he asked, would you sell yourself?
Sorry. Are you okay?
Yes. Thank you.
How much?
What?
I heard you would do everything Minhyeok ask to pay off the debt.
I'll pay off the debt for you.
Would you do everything I ask you to do?
It's not like that.
Then...
You look beautiful.
I like it. Come here.
Are you crazy? Hey! Come here!
Stay still.
Stop.
You're substandard product.
Get up!
What is it?
You still have a bad taste.
What happened?
She'd do anything for money, right?
Don't prentend to be noble.
Go buy a clothes.
Minhyeok, look at the wound.
She'd do anything.
Only for me.
You bastard.
What's going on? Where's Gwangsu?
I don't know.
Yes. What?
A board meeting at this time
What? Dismissal?
Jo Minhyeok. I'll forgive you this time, but I won't let it slide again.
Let's wati and see.
You're going to pay for this.
Substandard product, I'll see you again.
Yes.
They came together.
The owner said he proposed to her on that night.
When was it?
On the same night.
Are you sure?
Yes. It was the night of the accident.
Due to a business slump, a high vacancy rate,
and a scandal regarding the Incheon Harbor,
we're here to discuss Jo Minhyeok's dismissal.
I think I have enough shares to attend the meeting.
- What? - The board meeting wants to dismiss Joe Minhyeok.
I can't believe this! How many will be against it?
More than half of the members will vote against it if you want them to.
Call them.
Why don't we start the vote?
We'll start the vote regarding to the dismissal of Jo Minhyeok.
If you're in favor, raise your hand.
Let's go, don't stay here.
What are you doing?
What are you thinking about?